martinmadsen

software developer, me@martinbjeldbak.com

about

melbourne australia

32 years old +61 413 043 210 martinbjeldbak.com nartinbjeldbak in / martinbjeldbak

languages danish, english

programming

Golang, Python GitHub Actions Ruby on Rails SOL, Docker AWS, GCP LATEX, HTML, Git JavaScript, Python OS X, Unix

interests

continuous delivery machine learning devOps architecture web development self-hosting

experience

since 2020 **Software Engineer**

ANZ Bank, Melbourne, Australia Working on ANZ Plus as software engineer. I am responsible for designing, implementing, & maintaining infrastructure, microservices, DevSecOps pipelines, mainly using GitHub Actions and Golang. I work with architects, tech leads, and security team members to deliver features that support the bank across a multitude of areas. Since starting, I have worked in two core

teams.

2016-2020 Lead Software Developer, Backend

NetEngine, Brisbane, Australia Ruby on Rails software developer working with consultancy clients to build web-based systems across many different industries, from finance to flood mapping. I worked on setting up infrastructure in AWS to building GraphQL Rails APIs. I also partook in non-technical activities, such as business planning, training new backend developers. Clients include Apollo Motorhome Holidays.

2012-2014 **Student Software Developer**

Falck Healthcare a/s, Aalborg, Denmark

Development of Ruby on Rails-based system used daily by ca. 40 of Falck's physiotherapists to journal their patients' treatments and wellbeing.

education

2014-2016 M.Sc. in Computer Science Aalborg University (AAU), Denmark

Majoring in Computer Science (120 ECTS)

Specializing in Machine Intelligence

2014-2015 Studying abroad University of California, San Diego (UCSD), USA

Fully accredited as part of the first year of my master's degree from Aalborg

University

2011-2014 B.Sc. in Computer Science

Aalborg University (AAU), Denmark

Majoring in Computer Science (180 ECTS)

projects

since 2024 Shotta O / martinbjeldbak/Shotta

World of Warcraft addon to take screenshots at user-defined intervals. Written

in Lua. 1500+ downloads.

since 2022 Self-hosted / martinbjeldbak/self-hosted

Open-sourced my local docker-compose configuration running on my home

2016 A Hierarchical Tree Distance Measure for Classification

thesis.pdf

Concluded my M.Sc. degree. Published in Proceedings of the 6th International Conference on Pattern Recognition Applications and Methods - Volume

1: ICPRAM 2017, pages 502-509